Guide to the Stephen M. Cabrinety Collection in the History of Microcomputing, ca. 1975-1995
Department of Special Collections
- Software, Series 1
  - Games, Subseries 1.4
    - Sega Enterprises, Ltd. Thunderground, 1983, 1 computer cartridgeAtari (Box 207)
    - Sega Enterprises, Ltd. Turbo Out Run, 1989, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 193)
    - Sega Inc. Aerial Assault, 1992, computer cartridgeSEGA Game Gear (Box 11)
    - Sega of America Aerial Assault, 1990, computer cartridgeSega (Box 11)
    - Sega of America Gunstar Heroes, 1993, computer cartridgeGenesis (Sega) (Box 6)
    - Sega of America Jurassic Park, 1993, computer cartridgeGenesis (Sega) (Box 6)
    - Sega of America Kid Chameleon, 1992, computer cartridgeGenesis (Sega) (Box 6)
    - Sega of America Outrun 2019, 1993, computer cartridgeGenesis (Sega) (Box 7)
    - Sega of America Ranger X, 1993, computer cartridgeGenesis (Sega) (Box 7)
    - Sega of America Shinobi III: Return of the Ninja Master, 1993, computer cartridgeGenesis (Sega) (Box 7)
    - Sega of America Sports Talk Football '93, 1992, computer cartridgeGenesis (Sega) (Box 7)
    - Sega of America World Heroes, 1994, computer cartridgeGenesis (Sega) (Box 7)
    - Sega of America Young Indiana Jones: Instruments of Chaos, 1994, computer cartridgeGenesis (Sega) (Box 7)
    - Sega of America, Inc. Astro Warrior: The Mega Cartridge, 1986, 1 computer cartridgeSEGA (Box 11)
    - Sega of America, Inc. Cyberball, 1990, 1 computer cartridgeSega Genesis (Box 208)
    - Sega of America, Inc. Cyborg Justice, 1989, 1 computer cartridgeSega Genesis (Box 208)
    - Sega of America, Inc. Cyborg Justice, 1993, 1 computer cartridgeSega Genesis (Box 208)
    - Sega of America, Inc. Dick Tracy, 1990, 1 computer cartridgeSega Genesis (Box 208)
    - Sega of America, Inc. Eternal Champions, 1993, 1 computer cartridgeSega Genesis (Box 208)
    - Sega of America, Inc. Fatal Labyrinth, 1991, 1 computer cartridgeSega Genesis (Box 208)
    - Sega of America, Inc. Forgotten Worlds, 1989, 1 computer cartridgeSega Genesis (Box 208)
    - Sega of America, Inc. Ghost House, 1986, 1 computer cartridgeSega (Box 207)
    - Sega Of America Inc Ghostbusters, 1990, 1 computer cartridgeSega Genesis (Box 208)
    - Sega of America, Inc. Great Baseball: The Mega Cartridge, 1987, 1 computer cartridgeSEGA (Box 11)
    - Sega of America, Inc. Great Soccer: The Mega Cartridge, 1987, 1 computer cartridgeSEGA (Box 11)
    - Sega of America, Inc. Great Volleyball: The Mega Cartridge, 1987, 1 computer cartridgeSEGA (Box 11)
    - Sega of America, Inc. Great Volleyball: The Mega Cartridge, 1987, 1 computer cartridgeSEGA (Box 11)
    - Sega of America, Inc. Herzog Zwei, 1990, 1 computer cartridgeGenesis (Sega) (Box 40)
    - Sega of America, Inc. Last Battle, 1989, 1 computer cartridgeSega Genesis (Box 208)
    - Sega of America, Inc. McDonald's Treasure Island Adventure, 1993, 1 computer cartridgeSega Genesis (Box 208)
    - Sega of America, Inc. Michael Jackson's Moonwalker, 1990, 1 computer cartridgeSega Genesis (Box 208)
    - Sega of America, Inc. Missile Defense 3-D: The Mega Cartridge, 1987, 1 computer cartridgeSEGA (Box 11)
    - Sega of America, Inc. Mystic Defender, 1989, 1 computer cartridgeSega Genesis (Box 208)
    - Sega of America, Inc. Pat Riley Basketball, 1990, 1 computer cartridgeSega Genesis (Box 208)
    - Sega of America, Inc. Quartet: The Mega Cartridge, 1987, 1 computer cartridgeSEGA (Box 11)
    - Sega of America, Inc. Quartet: The Mega Cartridge, 1987, 1 computer cartridgeSEGA (Box 11)
    - Sega of America, Inc. Shooting Gallery: The Mega Cartridge, 1987, 1 computer cartridgeSEGA (Box 11)
    - Sega of America, Inc. Sonic the Hedgehog 2, 1992, 1 computer cartridgeSega Genesis (Box 207)
    - Sega of America, Inc. Space Harrier II, 1989, 1 computer cartridgeSega Genesis (Box 208)
    - Sega of America, Inc. Sports Pad Football, 1987, 1 computer cartridgeSega (Box 40)
    - Sega of America, Inc. Strider, 1990, 1 computer cartridgeSega Genesis (Box 208)
    - Sega of America, Inc. Super Tennis, 1986, 1 computer cartridgeSega (Box 40)
    - Sega of America, Inc. ToeJam & Earl in Panic on Funkotron, 1993, 1 computer cartridgeSega Genesis (Box 208)
    - Sega of America, Inc. TransBot, 1986, 1 computer cartridgeSega (Box 40)
    - Sega of America, Inc. Triple Score 3 Games in 1: Super Hang-on/ Columns/ WC Soccer, 1993, 1 computer cartridgeSega Genesis (Box 208)
    - Sega of America, Ltd. Gunstar Heroes, 1993, 1 computer cartridgeSega Genesis (Box 207)
    - Sega of America, Ltd. Sports Talk Baseball, 1992, 1 computer cartridgeSega Genesis (Box 207)
    - Seika Corporation Drakkhen, 1991, computer cartridgeSuper Nintendo (Box 8)
    - Seika Corporation Snoopy's Magic Show, 1990, 1 computer cartridgeGame Boy (Nintendo) (Box 202)
    - Seismic, Inc. Air Diver, 1990, 1 computer cartridgeSega Genesis (Box 208)
    - Seismic, Inc. Super Hydlide, 1990, 1 computer cartridgeGenesis (Sega) (Box 40)
    - Seismic Software, Inc. Musha: Metallic Uniframe Super Hybrid Armor, 1990, computer cartridgeGenesis (Sega) (Box 7)
    - Selectware Software Jukebox, 1992, 1 computer laser optical disc; 4 ¾ in.DOS (Box 159)
    - Sensible Software Disk Organizer, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 45)
    - Sentient Software, Inc. Gold Rush, 1982, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 168)
    - SETA USA, Inc. Cacoma Knight in Bizyland, 1993, computer cartridgeSuper Nintendo (Box 8)
    - SETA USA, Inc. Formula One Built to Win F-1 B.T.W., 1990, computer cartridgeNintendo (Box 10)
    - SETA USA, Inc. Kendo Rage, 1993, computer cartridgeSuper Nintendo (Box 9)
    - Seymor-Radix IMG: Scan, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 129)
    - Share Data Backgammon, 1986, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 157)
    - Share Data Crossword Puzzles Volume III, 1984, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. DOS (Box 157)
    - Share Data, Inc. Action Thrillers, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 197)
    - Share Data, Inc. Arcade Action, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 197)
    - Share Data, Inc. Arcade SnapDragon, 1988, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 193)
    - Share Data, Inc. Arcade Star Quake, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 200)
    - Share Data, Inc. Calendar & Stationery, 1986, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 160)
    - Share Data, Inc. Casino Challenge, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 197)
    - Share Data, Inc. Child's Play, 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 197)
    - Share Data, Inc. Dell Crossword Puzzles Volume III, 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 193)
    - Share Data, Inc. Family Fued Official T.V. Game Show Program, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 187)
    - Share Data, Inc. Graphics Master, 1987, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 165)
    - Share Data, Inc. Jeopardy! Official T.V. Game Show Program, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 187)
    - Share Data, Inc. Leisure Time Classics, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 197)
    - Share Data, Inc. StarQuake, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 160)
    - Share Data, Inc. Survival Instinct featuring Wrong Way Racer & Frog Bog, 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 197)
    - Share Data, Inc. Warp Rangers featuring Ollo 1 & Ollo II, 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 197)
    - Share Data, Inc. Wheel of Fortune! Official T.V. Game Show Program, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 187)
    - Sharedata Arcade Adventures, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 26)
    - Sharedata Awesome Earl in SkateRock, 1988, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 60)
    - Sharedata Blackjack, 1986, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 61)
    - Sharedata Casino Challenge, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 28)
    - Sharedata Chess Challengers, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 28)
    - Sharedata Children's Collection, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 28)
    - Sharedata Family Feud: official t.v. game show program software, 1987, 2 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 121)
    - Sharedata Jeopardy!, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 21)
    - Sharedata Jeopardy: official t.v. game show program software, 1987, 2 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 121)
    - Sharedata Jeopardy! T.V. Game Show, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 173)
    - Sharedata Racing Simulation Games, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 182)
    - Sharedata Skaterock, 1988, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 182)
    - Sharedata Starquake, 1988, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 69)
    - Sharedata Wheel of Fortune: Official T.V. Game Show, 1987, computer disk; 3 ½ in. Apple (Box 112)
    - Sharedata World Cup Soccer, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 176)
    - ShareData, Inc. Blackjack, 1986, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 160)
    - Sharedata, Inc. "Family Feud" official T.V. game show program, 1987, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 170)
    - Sharedata, Inc. "Wheel of Fortune" official T.V. game show program, 1987, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 170)
    - Shareware Unlimited Frac, 1995, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Windows 3.1 (Box 219)
    - Shareware Unlimited Scud Attack, 1995, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Windows 3.1 (Box 219)
    - Showcase Software Astro Patrol, 1983, 1 computer cassetteCommodore VIC-20 (Box 93)
    - Showcase Software Doughboy, 1983, 1 computer cassetteCommodore VIC-20 (Box 93)
    - Showcase Software Salmon Run, 1983, 1 computer cassetteCommodore VIC-20 (Box 93)
    - Showcase Software Squeeze, 1983, 1 computer cassetteCommodore VIC-20 (Box 93)
    - Sierra On-line Crossfire, 1981, 1 computer cassetteAtari (Box 79)
    - Sierra On-line Crossfire, 1981, 1 computer cassetteAtari (Box 79)
    - Sierra On-line Dragon's Keep, 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 29)
    - Sierra On-line Dragon's Keep, 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 184)
    - Sierra On-Line Gelfing Adventure, 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 46)
    - Sierra On-line Man Hunter New York, 1988, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 65)
    - Sierra On-Line Mixed-up Mother Goose, n.d., 1 computer laser optical disc; 4 ¾ in.DOS (Box 171)
    - Sierra On-line Sammy Lightfoot, 1983, 1 computer cartridgeCommodore (Box 35)
    - Sierra On-line Stunt Flyer, 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 36)
    - Sierra On-line Stunt Flyer, 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 198)
    - Sierra On-line Wrath of Denethenor, 1986, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 38)
    - Sierra On-line Wrath of Denethenor, 1986, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 59)
    - Sierra On-Line, Inc. Aquatron, 1983, 1 computer cartridgeAtari (Box 24)
    - Sierra On-Line, Inc. Cannonball Blitz, 1982, 1 computer cartridgeCommodore VIC-20 (Box 211)
    - Sierra On-Line, Inc. Creepy Corridors, n.d., 1 computer cartridgeCommodore VIC-20 (Box 209)
    - Sierra On-Line, Inc. Creepy Corridors, n.d., 1 computer cartridgeCommodore VIC-20 (Box 211)
    - Sierra On-Line, Inc. Crossfire, 1981, 1 computer cartridgeCommodore VIC-20 (Box 212)
    - Sierra On-Line, Inc. Ecoquest: The Search for Cetus, n.d., 1 computer laser optical disc; 4 ¾ in.DOS (Box 164)
    - Sierra On-Line, Inc. Freddy Pharkas Frontier Pharmacist, 1993, 2 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. MS-DOS (Box 4)
    - Sierra On-line, Inc. Golf Challenge, 1981, 1 computer cassetteAtari (Box 85)
    - Sierra On-Line, Inc. Helicopter Simulator, 1987, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 165)
    - Sierra On-line, Inc. Jawbreaker, n.d., 1 computer cassetteAtari (Box 127)
    - Sierra On-line Inc King's Quest, 1984, computer disk; 3 ½ in. Apple (Box 120)
    - Sierra On-line Inc King's Quest II: Romancing the Throne, 1987, computer disk; 3 ½ in. Macintosh (Box 113)
    - Sierra On-line Inc King's Quest II: Romancing the Throne, 1985, computer disk; 3 ½ in. Apple (Box 124)
    - Sierra On-Line, Inc. King's Quest III: To Heir is Human, 1986, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Amiga (Box 41)
    - Sierra On-line Inc King's Quest III: To Heir is Human, 1987, computer disk; 3 ½ in. Macintosh (Box 113)
    - Sierra On-line Inc King's Quest: Quest for the Crown, 1987, computer disk; 3 ½ in. Macintosh (Box 113)
    - Sierra On-line, Inc. King's Quest V: Absence makes the heart go yonder!, 1990, 1 computer laser optical disc; 4 ¾ in.DOS (Box 159)
    - Sierra On-line, Inc. King's Quest VI: Heir Today, Gone Tomorrow, 1993, computer laser optical disc; 4 ¾ in.MS-DOS (Box 12)
    - Sierra On-Line, Inc. Leisure Suit Larry goes Looking for Love (in several wrong places), 1988, computer disk; 5 ¼ in.; 3 ½ in.DOS (Box 166)
    - Sierra On-line Inc Leisure Suit Larry in The Land of the Lounge Lizards: a 3-D Animated Adventure Game, 1987, computer disk; 3 ½ in. Apple (Box 113)
    - Sierra On-Line, Inc. Lunar Leeper, 1983, 1 computer cartridgeCommodore VIC-20 (Box 211)
    - Sierra On-line Inc Mr Cool, created by Peter Oliphant, n.d., 1 computer cartridgeAtari (Box 87)
    - Sierra On-Line, Inc. Pest Patrol, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 116)
    - Sierra On-Line Inc. Sierra Championship Boxing, 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 184)
    - Sierra On-Line Inc. Sierra Championship Boxing, 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 188)
    - Sierra On-Line, Inc. Slipheed, 1988, 1 computer cartridgeTandy (Box 217)
    - Sierra On-line Inc Space Quest: a 3-D Animated Adventure Game, 1987, computer disk; 3 ½ in. Macintosh (Box 113)
    - Sierra On-Line, Inc. Space Quest: the Sarien Encounter, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in.; 3 ½ in.DOS (Box 157)
    - Sierra On-Line, Inc. Thexder, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Tandy (Box 217)
    - Sierra On-line, Inc. Threshold, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 139)
    - Sierra On-Line, Inc. Threshold, 1983, 1 computer cassetteCommodore VIC-20 (Box 212)
    - Sierra On-Line, Inc. Trial By Fire, 1990, computer disk; 5 ¼ in.; 3 ½ in.DOS (Box 165)
    - Sierra On-Line, Inc. Troll's Tale, 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 198)
    - Sierra On-Line, Inc. Ultima II, 1985, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 108)
    - Sierra On-Line, Inc. Ultima II, 1984, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 166)
    - Sierra On-Line, Inc. Ultima II, 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 197)
    - Sierra On-Line, Inc. Ultima II: The Revenge of the Enchantress, 1984, computer disk; 3 ½ in. Macintosh (Box 112)
    - Sierra Vision Official Frogger, 1983, 1 computer cassetteAtari (Box 134)
    - Sight & Sound Music Software, Inc. On Stage computer song album [2 copies], 1984, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 186)
    - Silicon Beach Software Enchanted Scepters, featuring RealSound, 1984, computer disk; 3 ½ in. Macintosh (Box 112)
    - Silmarils Manhattan Dealers, 1988, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 151)
    - Silmarils Starblade, n.d., computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Amiga (Box 111)
    - Sim Computer Products, Inc. Colorcraft Demo, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore VIC-20 (Box 93)
    - Sim Computer Products, Inc. Kentucky Derby BLS-GA03, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore VIC-20 (Box 93)
    - Simon and Schuster Software # Cruncher: The Complete Spreadsheet, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in.; 3 ½ in.DOS (Box 160)
    - Simon and Schuster Software Webster's NewWorld Combo, n.d., computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 165)
    - Simon & Schuster, Inc. Star Trek: the kobayashi alternative, 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 36)
    - Simon & Schuster, Inc. Star Trek: the Promethean Prophecy, 1986, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 197)
    - Simon & Schuster Software Star Trek: First Contact, 1988, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Atari (Box 141)
    - Sir-Tech Software, Inc. Crypt Medea: an adventure game for the very mature and strong of heart. (the cover picture is really scary...), 1983, computer disk; 3 ½ in. Apple (Box 6)
    - Sir-Tech Software, Inc. Crypt of Medea, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 125)
    - Sir-Tech Software, Inc. Galactic Attack, 1982, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 46)
    - Sir-Tech Software, Inc. Galactic Attack, 1982, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 116)
    - Sir-Tech Software, Inc. Rescue Raiders, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 137)
    - Sir-Tech Software, Inc. Space Combat Simulation Deep Space Operation Copernicus, 1987, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 112)
    - Sir-tech Software, Inc. Space Combat Simulation Deep Space: Operation Copernicus, 1986, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 201)
    - Sir-Tech Software, Inc. Star Maze: A Hi-Res Arcade Game, 1982, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 6)
    - Sir-tech Software Inc Wizardry, 1981, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 59)
    - Sirius Repton, 1982, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 182)
    - Sirius Twerps, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 139)
    - Sirius Software Bandits, 1982, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 82)
    - Sirius Software Worm War I, 1982, 1 computer cartridgeAtari (Box 23)
    - Sirius Software, Inc. Bandits, 1982, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 138)
    - Sirius Software, Inc. Fast Eddie, n.d., computer cartridgeAtari (Box 145)
    - Sirius Software, Inc. Fast Eddie, 1982, 1 computer cartridgeCommodore VIC-20 (Box 212)
    - Sirius Software, Inc. Snake Byte, 1982, 2 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 119)
    - Sirius Software, Inc. Snake Byte, 1982, 2 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 182)
    - Sirius Software, Inc. Sneakers, 1980, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 127)
    - Sirius Software, Inc. Sneakers, 1980, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 131)
    - Sirius Software, Inc. Sneakers, 1980, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 131)
    - Sirius Software, Inc. Spider City, 1983, 1 computer cartridgeAtari (Box 131)
    - Sirius Software, Inc. Squish 'em, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 134)
    - Sirius Software, Inc. Squish 'em, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 183)
    - Sirius Software, Inc. Turmoil, 1982, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 183)
    - Sirius Software, Inc. Type Attack, 1983, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 167)
    - Slash Corporation Take Ten CD-ROM, 1994, computer laser optical disc; 4 ¾ in.DOS (Box 175)
    - Slash Corporation Take Ten CD-ROM (utilities) (shareware), 1995, computer laser optical disc; 4 ¾ in.DOS (Box 175)
    - SmartWorks Student Word Processor with Outliner, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in.; 3 ½ in.DOS (Box 157)
    - SNK Corporation Crystalis, 1990, 1 computer cartridgeNintendo (Box 202)
    - SNK Corporation Ikari Warriors, 1988, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 200)
    - SNK Corporation of America P.O.W.: Prisoners of War, 1989, 1 computer cartridgeNintendo (Box 40)
    - Sofel, Inc. Wall Street Kid, 1990, 1 computer cartridgeNintendo (Box 202)
    - Softbit, Inc. Power Tools: over 3000 shareware programs for DOS, 1992, computer laser optical disc; 4 ¾ in.DOS (Box 175)
    - Softdisk Softdisk: the monthly software collection for people who love Apple II computers.--No. 72, 1987, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 6)
    - Softgang Final Trip, 1987, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Amiga (Box 41)
    - Softgold Street Gang, 1987, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Amiga (Box 99)
    - Softie Incorporated Computer Crosswords, 1984, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 179)
    - Softie Incorporated Computer Crosswords, vol. 2, 1984, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 166)
    - Softie Incorporated Computer Crosswords, volume 2, 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 116)
    - Softie Incorporated The New York Times Computer Crossword Puzzles by Computer Crosswords, vol. 2, 1984, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 111)
    - Softie Incorporated The New York Times Computer Crossword Puzzles by Computer Crosswords, vol. 2, 1984, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 166)
    - Softie Incorporated The New York Times Computer Crossword Puzzles by Computer Crosswords, 1984, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 179)
    - Softron, Inc. Pizza Time [2 copies], 1983, 2 computer cassetteCommodore VIC-20 (Box 39)
    - Softsmith Software Abuse, 1981, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 130)
    - Softsmith Software Firebird, n.d., computer disk; 3 ½ in. Apple (Box 109)
    - Softsmith Software Head On, 1982, 1 computer cassetteCommodore VIC-20 (Box 212)
    - Softsmith Software Match Racer, 1981, 1 computer cassetteAtari (Box 130)
    - Softsmith Software Pollywog, 1982, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 125)
    - Softsmith Software Rainbow Forest, 1981, 1 computer cassetteTRS-80 (Box 215)
    - Softsmith Software Regilian Worm, 1982, 1 computer cassetteTRS-80 (Box 215)
    - Softsmith Software Softsmith Spox, 1982, 1 computer cassetteTRS-80 (Box 26)
    - Softsmith Software Space Chase, 1982, 1 computer cassetteTRS-80 (Box 26)
    - Softsmith Software The Catch, 1982, 1 computer cassetteCommodore VIC-20 (Box 38)
    - Softsmith Software Tic Tac Show Sports Facts, 1982, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 117)
    - Softsmith Software, Inc. The Exterminator, 1982, 1 computer cassetteCommodore VIC-20 (Box 211)
    - Softstream International, Inc. Colour Billiards, n.d., computer disk; 3 ½ in. Macintosh (Box 105)
    - Softstream International, Inc. Mac Man, n.d., computer disk; 3 ½ in. Macintosh (Box 105)
    - Softstream International, Inc. The Solitaire Desk Accessory, n.d., computer disk; 3 ½ in. Macintosh (Box 105)
    - Softsync, Inc. Kid Pro Quo, 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 176)
    - Software Applications Specialists Stealth, 1982, 1 computer cassetteAtari (Box 209)
    - Software Country Computer Software Classics Golden Oldies Volume 1: Adventure, Eliza, Life, Pong, n.d., 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Amiga (Box 97)
    - Software Investments Plus, Inc. Destiny Adventure Game, 1985, Apple (Box 45)
    - Software Publishing Corporation PFS: access, 1985, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 174)
    - Software Sorcery Jutland, 1993, computer laser optical disc; 4 ¾ in.MS-DOS (Box 20)
    - Software Toolworks Beyond the Black Hole, n.d., computer disk; 3 ½ in. DOS (Box 162)
    - Software Toolworks The Chessmaster 2000, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 155)
    - Solutions, Inc. Smart Scrap and the Clipper, n.d., 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Macintosh (Box 121)
    - Sony Imagesoft Bram Stoker's Dracula, 1991, computer cartridgeNintendo (Box 10)
    - Sony Imagesoft Chuck Rock, 1992, computer cartridgeGame Boy (Nintendo) (Box 8)
    - Sony Imagesoft Cliff Hanger, 1993, 1 computer cartridgeSEGA Game Gear (Box 207)
    - Sony Imagesoft Cliffhanger, 1991, computer cartridgeGame Boy (Nintendo) (Box 8)
    - Sony Imagesoft Cliffhanger, 1993, computer cartridgeNintendo (Box 10)
    - Sony Imagesoft, Cliffhanger, 1994, 1 computer laser optical disc; 4 ¾ in.SEGA CD (Box 23)
    - Sony Imagesoft Gear Works, 1992, 1 computer cartridgeSEGA Game Gear (Box 207)
    - Sony Imagesoft Mary Shelley's Frankenstein, 1994, 1 computer cartridgeSega Genesis (Box 208)
    - Sony Imagesoft, Inc. Chuck Rock, 1992, 1 computer laser optical disc; 4 ¾ in.SEGA CD (Box 23)
    - Sony Imagesoft, Inc. Extra Innings, 1991, computer cartridgeSuper Nintendo (Box 8)
    - Sony Imagesoft, Inc. Power Factory: featuring C+C Music Factory, 1992, 1 computer laser optical disc; 4 ¾ in.SEGA CD (Box 23)
    - Spectravideo International, Ltd. Planet Patrol, 1983, 1 computer cartridgeColecoVision & ADAM (Box 213)
    - Spectravision Spectron, 1983, 1 computer cartridgeColecoVision & ADAM (Box 213)
    - Spectrum Computers Galactic Chase, 1981, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 134)
    - Spectrum HoloByte Falcon, 1987, computer disk; 3 ½ in. Macintosh (Box 125)
    - Spectrum Holobyte Falcon: the F-16 Fighter Simulation, 1987, computer disk; 5 ¼ in.; 3 ½ in.DOS (Box 170)
    - Spectrum Holobyte Soldiers of Fortune, 1993, computer cartridgeGenesis (Sega) (Box 7)